{
	"questions" : [
		{
			"id" : 1,
			"question" : "Which of the following is correct about callbacks?",
			"options" : [
				"A callback is a plain JavaScript function passed to some method as an argument or option.",
				"Some callbacks are just events, called to give the user a chance to react when a certain state is triggered.",
				"Both of the above.",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 2,
			"question" : "Which of the following is the correct syntax to create a cookie using JavaScript?",
			"options" : [
				"document.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';",
				"browser.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';",
				"window.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';",
				"navigator.cookie = 'key1 = value1; key2 = value2; expires = date';"
			],
			"answer" : 0
		},
		{
			"id" : 3,
			"question" : "Which built-in method combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
			"options" : [
				"append()",
				"concat()",
				"attach()",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"answer" : 1
		},
		{
			"id" : 4,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of Number object forces a number to display in exponential notation?",
			"options" : [
				"toExponential()",
				"toFixed()",
				"toPrecision()",
				"toLocaleString()"
			],
			"answer" : 0
		},
		{
			"id" : 5,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of String object combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
			"options" : [
				"add()",
				"merge()",
				"concat()",
				"append()"
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 6,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of String object extracts a section of a string and returns a new string?",
			"options" : [
				"slice()",
				"split()",
				"replace()",
				"search()"
			],
			"answer" : 0
		},
		{
			"id" : 7,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of String object creates a string to blink as if it were in a <blink> tag?",
			"options" : [
				"anchor()",
				"big()",
				"blink()",
				"italics()"
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 8,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as struck-out text, as if it were in a <strike> tag?",
			"options" : [
				"sup()",
				"small()",
				"strike()",
				"sub()"
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 9,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of Array object returns the first (least) index of an element within the array equal to the specified value, or -1 if none is found?",
			"options" : [
				"indexOf()",
				"join()",
				"lastIndexOf()",
				"map()"
			],
			"answer" : 0
		},
		{
			"id" : 10,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of Array object returns a string representing the array and its elements?",
			"options" : [
				"slice()",
				"sort()",
				"splice()",
				"toString()"
			],
			"answer" : 3
		},
		{
			"id" : 11,
			"question" : "Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?",
			"options" : [
				"while()",
				"loop()",
				"forEach()",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 12,
			"question" : "Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array?",
			"options" : [
				"changeOrder(order)",
				"reverse()",
				"sort(order)",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"answer" : 1
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of Boolean object returns a string of either 'true' or 'false' depending upon the value of the object?",
			"options" : [
				"toSource()",
				"valueOf()",
				"toString()",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location through the specified number of characters?",
			"options" : [
				"slice()",
				"split()",
				"substr()",
				"search()"
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 15,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
			"options" : [
				"toLocaleLowerCase()",
				"toLowerCase()",
				"toString()",
				"substring()"
			],
			"answer" : 1
		},
		{
			"id" : 16,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of Array object returns a new array comprised of this array joined with other array(s) and/or value(s)?",
			"options" : [
				"concat()",
				"pop()",
				"push()",
				"some()"
			],
			"answer" : 0
		},
		{
			"id" : 17,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of Array object calls a function for each element in the array?",
			"options" : [
				"concat()",
				"every()",
				"filter()",
				"forEach()"
			],
			"answer" : 3
		},
		{
			"id" : 18,
			"question" : "Which of the following function of Array object removes the first element from an array and returns that element?",
			"options" : [
				"reverse()",
				"some()",
				"shift()",
				"slice()"
			],
			"answer" : 2
		},
		{
			"id" : 19,
			"question" : "Which of the following type of variable is visible everywhere in your JavaScript code?",
			"options" : [
				"global variable",
				"local variable",
				"Both of the above.",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"answer" : 0
		},
		{
			"id" : 20,
			"question" : "Which built-in method returns the character at the specified index?",
			"options" : [
				"characterAt()",
				"getCharAt()",
				"charAt()",
				"None of the above."
			],
			"answer" : 2
		}
	]
}